proxybrowsing.com 2015-05-13

# Proxy Browsing - Anonymous Web Browser

## Privacy Policy:

Your privacy is important to us. We wish for you to be fully informed of how your information is gathered and used. 

**What information do we gather?**  
We do not require any personal information from you to use our proxy service   
However, we do maintain logs for up to 7 days on all user activity via our proxy website.   
This includes, but is not limited to, information such as   
(a) your IP address  
(b) the date and time (Unix Timestamp)  
(c) and your browser (HTTP_USER_AGENT)  
(d) the referring page (HTTP_REFERER)

Other information may also be logged at our discretion.

We do 

_**NOT**_ log sensitive data such as **usernames and passwords** sent through forms using POST.

**How we use gathered information:**  
We will not share any information that we log about you with anybody at any time unless for reasons, including but not limited to, **law enforcement**.   
We do not, and **will not sell any of the information logged.** We value your privacy and will make every effort to prevent a third party from having us disclose our logs, but we reserve the right to cooperate with law enforcement enquires. This includes but is not limited to, law enforcement officials who are investigating criminal activities committed by users of our service. 

**How we protect your information:**  
We make every effort to secure our servers by applying the latest updates if applicable, and securing log locations. 

**Cookies:**  
Cookies are used to better your experience. You can disable cookies if you wish using browser settings or any other program. However, this could affect your ability to use features such as logging in or using other aspects of our service. Our advertisement providers can also use cookies for tracking purposes and display ads.

**Third Party Advertisements**  
We use third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site and hosted boards. These companies may collect and use information about your visits to our website as well as other web sites.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.   
If you would like more information please visit the following links: 

By using any part of our service, you agree to the terms of the following advertisers listed above in addition to the terms of this privacy policy. 

**Modifications to our Policy:**  
We may update and revise this privacy policy with, or without notice to you.

**Proxy Site Lists :[Fresh Proxy List](http://www.freshproxylist.com/) \- [Top Proxies](http://www.topproxies.org/) \- [IP Hide](http://www.ip-hide.com/) \- [Proxy Servers](http://www.proxyservers.info/)**
